PRODUCT DESIGNER CONTACT

Michael Perez

mikeperezdigital.com/hire hi@mikeperezdigital.com

I'm a Product Designer from the United States that solves business problems with humancentered design methodologies. I recently worked in the Czech Republic to learn about how humans tick on the other side of the pond.

Work Experience

LEAD DESIGNER

Honeywell - Joule

May 2019 - Present

In this role, I work with various marketing and product teams to rethink our web, ecommerce, and product experiences.

LEAD DESIGNER

Honeywell - Brno, Czech Republic

October 2018 - April 2019

Spent 6 months evangelizing design best practices in Honeywell's Brno Technology Hub.

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Honeywell Sentience™

October 2016 - September 2018

In this role, I worked with an agile, cross-functional team of Product Managers, Software Engineers, and UX Designers for Honeywell's internal start up, Sentience™. I delivered user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and visual designs for the Honeywell Sentience™ IoT, Data, & Analytics experiences

UX DESIGNER

Honeywell

May 2015 - September 2016

In this role, I worked with multiple principle designers and agencies on Honeywell's Digital Workplace, our company wide intranet used by 100,000 + users. We conducted global user research and usability testing in 3 global regions: APAC, EMEA, and North America.

Education

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND ENTREPRENEURSHIP

Rutgers University / New Brunswick, New Jersey